Women's Music Archives Collection
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. ARTIST FILES
  - Izquierda 1977-80, undated (Box 4)
  - J (Box 4)
  - Jade and Sarsaparillaundated (Box 4)
  - Jan and Ilse 1993-94, undated (Box 4)
  - Jane Doe Band 1982-83, undated (Box 4)
  - Jasmine 1982-87, undated (Box 4)
  - Javanaise 1982, undated (Box 4)
  - Jones, Diana 1996-97, undated (Box 4)
  - Joy, Susanundated (Box 4)
  - Justice, Jennifer 1985, undated (Box 4)
  - Justina and Joyce 1989-95, undated (Box 4)
  - Jyosna (Jordan) 1985-93, undated (Box 4)
  - K (Box 4)
  - Kaldor, Connie 1982-86, undated (Box 4)
  - Karen Beth 1977-88, undated (Box 4)
  - Kay, Hillary 1986-90, undated (Box 4)
  - Kelly, Julia 1989-90 (Box 4)
  - Keniston, Susan 1985-89, undated (Box 4)
  - Kid Sister 1987-88, undated (Box 4)
  - Koch, Lisa 1990-91, undated (Box 4)
  - Kolb, Elaine 1980-87, undated (Box 4)
  - Korantemaa, Nana 1990, undated (Box 4)
  - Krietlow, Marienne 1984-89, undated (Box 4)
  - Kron, Lisa 1989-91, undated (Box 4)
  - Kruisbrink, Annette 1996-98, undated (Box 4)
  - L (Box 4)
  - Labrys 1983-88, undated (Box 4)
  - Laduvane 1981-82, undated (Box 4)
  - Lady Be Good 1989, undated (Box 5)
  - Lamerduc, Anique 1993-94, undated (Box 5)
  - lang, k.d. 1993, undated (Box 5)
  - Langille, Suzanne 1985-86, undated (Box 5)
  - Larkin, Patty 1980-95, undated (Box 5)
  - Lavner, Lynn 1982, undated (Box 5)
  - Lems, Kristin 1976-85, undated (Box 5)
  - Les Amies Louisianaisesundated (Box 5)
  - Levoy, Debbie 1987-92, undated (Box 5)
  - Lewis, Zoe 1989-98, undated (Box 5)
  - Libana 1980-2006, undated (Box 5)
  - Lifeline 1983-90, undated (Box 5)
  - Lilah 1988-89, undated (Box 5)
  - Lindsay, Diane 1982-97, undated (Box 5)
  - Lippett, Betsy 1980-90, undated (Box 5)
  - Lorraine and Charlotte 1984, undated (Box 5)
  - Loulan, JoAnn 1987-88, undated (Box 5)
  - Love, Laura 1990-97, undated (Box 5)
  - Lovie Sizzle (Jackie Haywood) 1987-89, undated (Box 5)
  - Lucha 1975, undated (Box 5)
  - Lyons, Abbe 1981, undated (Box 5)
  - M (Box 5)
  - Manning, Cyd 1990, undated (Box 5)
  - McCalla, Dierdre 1982-2002, undated (Box 5)
  - McCall, Tulis 1980, undated (Box 5)
  - McClure, Kit 1986-2002, undated (Box 5)
  - McIlwaine, Ellen 1980-83, undated (Box 5)
  - McLaren, Libby 1988-89, undated (Box 5)
  - MacDonald, Betty 1982-96 (Box 5)
  - MacDonald, Carol 1985-86, undated (Box 5)
  - Mackay, Karen 1982-84, undated (Box 5)
  - Mama Quilla II 1980-81, undated (Box 5)
  - Marathon 1984-87, undated (Box 5)
  - Marie, Gayle 1982-84, undated (Box 5)
  - Marriechild and Goodman 1984-88, undated (Box 5)
  - Marilyn T. 1990-91, undated (Box 5)
  - Marley, Rita 1982, undated (Box 5)
  - Marmaluk, Daria 1979, 1990, undated (Box 5)
  - Masa 1992-97, undated (Box 5)
  - Mathis, Nick 1987-90 (Box 5)
  - Mayhew-Franks Quintet 1986-91, undated (Box 5)
  - Mermaids in the Basement 1992, undated (Box 5)
  - Midsummer Revels 1982-83 (Box 5)
  - Miller, Mev 1981-88, undated (Box 5)
  - MillingtonJune 1979-97, undated (Box 5)
  - Ming, Lee Pui 1991-92, undated (Box 5)
  - Mischief Mime 1983-85, undated (Box 5)
  - Mitchell, Joni 1981-2000 (Box 5)
  - Moaks, Linda 1984-89, undated (Box 5)
  - The Modern Fabricsundated (Box 5)
  - Molina, Jesse (Jesse X)1989, undated (Box 5)
  - Monk, Meredith 1988, undated (Box 5)
  - Monsur, Melanie 1987-90, undated (Box 5)
  - Montclair Women's Big Band 1996-2000, undated (Box 5)
  - Morgan and Phelanundated (Box 5)
  - Morgan, Hillary 1981, undated (Box 5)
  - Morgana 1980-93 (Box 5)
  - Morris, Bonnie 1994-99, undated (Box 5)
  - Morton, Jaime 1989, undated (Box 5)
  - Motherlode 1983-85, undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. Fun 1987-93, undated (Box 5)
  - Mullaney, Beth 1990-91, undated (Box 5)
  - MUSE (Cincinnati's Women's Choir) 1991-2005, undated (Box 5)
  - Musica Femina 1983-87, undated (Box 5)
  - N (Box 5)
  - Near, Holly
    - 1977-82 (Box 5)
    - 1983-2005, undated (Box 6)
  - New Haven Night Angels 1977 (Box 6)
  - New Haven Women's Chorus 1980 (Box 6)
  - Nichols and Potts 1990, undated (Box 6)
  - Noelle, Lori 1985-87, undated (Box 6)
  - No Regrets 1985-86, undated (Box 6)
  - Nolan, Dianne Marie 1990-91, undated (Box 6)
  - Nolan, Faith 1988-96, undated (Box 6)
  - Nuchow, Leslie 1990-91, undated (Box 6)
  - Nuru Dafina 1988-94, undated (Box 6)
  - O (Box 6)
  - Oakenstar, Jess Hawk 1990-92, undated (Box 6)
  - O'Donnell, Maureen 1984-85, undated (Box 6)
  - O'Hara and Laffey 1981, undated (Box 6)
  - On Second Thought 1988, undated (Box 6)
  - OVA 1980-88, undated (Box 6)
  - Ozer / Moore / Herrold 1983-86, undated (Box 6)
  - P (Box 6)
  - Pappas, Steph 1984-89, undated (Box 6)
  - Pat Graney Company, The 1985-92, undated (Box 6)
  - Pelham, Ruth 1981-87, undated (Box 6)
  - Petronella 1995-97, undated (Box 6)
  - Pierson, Suzanne 1971-83 (Box 6)
  - Pontopiddan, Lisa 1989-90, undated (Box 6)
  - Ponzio, Diane 1979-87, undated (Box 6)
  - Povinelli, Sharon 1989-90 (Box 6)
  - Powell, Linda 1979, undated (Box 6)
  - Powers, Doshie 1990-92, undated (Box 6)
  - Preeshl, Artemis 1987-91, undated (Box 6)
  - Presents of Mind 1991, undated (Box 6)
  - Psalms Music Ministry 1986, undated (Box 6)
  - Puckett and Personundated (Box 6)
  - R (Box 6)
  - Ragsdale, Georgia 1992-94, undated (Box 6)
  - Random Order 1992-93, undated (Box 6)
  - Reagan, Judy 1980, undated (Box 6)
  - Reagan, Bernice Johnson 1979-88, undated (Box 6)
  - Reagon, Toshi 1984-94, undated (Box 6)
  - RJ Nome / Rebecca Jane 1989-90, undated (Box 6)
  - Reed, Ann 1981-91, undated (Box 6)
  - Reynolds, Malvina 1964-2000, undated (Box 6)
  - Reynolds, Valerie 1987-93, undated (Box 6)
  - Rhiannon 1986-97, undated (Box 6)
  - Rhines, Marie 1976-85, undated (Box 7)
  - Rhode Island Feminist Chorus 1985-89, undated (Box 7)
  - Righteous Mothers, The 1985-92, undated (Box 7)
  - Ripley, Karen 1988-89, undated (Box 7)
  - Roadknight, Margret 1984-85, undated (Box 7)
  - Robbins, Jaime 1987-88, undated (Box 7)
  - Roberts, Carol 1981-83, undated (Box 7)
  - Robinson, Henrietta 1986-88, undated (Box 7)
  - The Roches 1979-97, undated (Box 7)
  - Roderick, Libby 1990-98, undated (Box 7)
  - Romantic Bonesundated (Box 7)
  - Rose, Betsy 1980-88, undated (Box 7)
  - Rose, Betsy and Cathy Winter 1979-86, undated (Box 7)
  - Rude Girls 1986-88, undated (Box 7)
  - Ruggles, Molly 1985, undated (Box 7)
  - Ryder, Sue 1986-88, undated (Box 7)
  - S (Box 7)
  - Salko, Keishya 1987, undated (Box 7)
  - San and Sabine 1987, undated (Box 7)
  - Sapphire 1985-90, undated (Box 7)
  - Sara Laughs 1987-88, undated (Box 7)
  - Savage, Maggie and Jude Fogelquist 1977-79, undated (Box 7)
  - Savell, Susan 1978-85, undated (Box 7)
  - Sawagi Taiko 1994-96 (Box 7)
  - Schwendinger, Leni 1980 (Box 7)
  - Scott, Nancy 2002, undated (Box 7)
  - Seale, Anne 1991, undated (Box 7)
  - Sellers, Maria 1989 (Box 7)
  - Shaffer, Tanya 1988-89, undated (Box 7)
  - Shanbaum, Suzanne 1981 (Box 7)
  - Shari and the Shy-Type 1985, undated (Box 7)
  - Shaw, Vickieundated (Box 7)
  - She 1986-87, undated (Box 7)
  - She Is 1991-97, undated (Box 7)
  - Shear, Linda 1976, undated (Box 7)
  - Sheets, Linda 1986-88, undated (Box 7)
  - Sherwood, Sherliundated (Box 7)
  - Shih, Patricia 1994-2000, undated (Box 7)
  - Shocked, Michelle 1988 (Box 7)
  - Shute, Sherry 1994-97, undated (Box 7)
  - Silver, Elaine 1979-89, undated (Box 7)
  - Silvermoon, Flash 1987-90, undated (Box 7)
  - Simmons, Woody 1981-89, undated (Box 7)
  - Siren 1985, undated (Box 7)
  - Sisson, Pam 1985-86, undated (Box 7)
  - Sister 1982, undated (Box 7)
  - Sloan, Judy 1980-91, undated (Box 7)
  - Slotoroff, Cyd 1980-2004, undated (Box 7)
  - Small, Judy 1984-86, undated (Box 7)
  - Software 1985, undated (Box 7)
  - Soloway, Faith 1997, undated (Box 7)
  - Sorrels, Rosalieundated (Box 7)
  - Souza, Susan 1997, undated (Box 7)
  - Spiderwoman Theater Companyundated (Box 7)
  - Spitz, Debbie 1986-89, undated (Box 7)
  - Squeeze Louise 1983, undated (Box 7)
  - Stato, Joanne 1989, undated (Box 7)
  - Stonewall Chorale 1980, undated (Box 7)
  - Strangers in Paradiseundated (Box 7)
  - Street People and Herson 1984-86, undated (Box 7)
  - Sudhalter, Carol 1985-86, undated (Box 7)
  - Suede 1984-2004, undated (Box 7)
  - Suhir 1991-95, undated (Box 7)
  - Sweet Honey in the Rock 1977-94, undated (Box 7)
  - Syli 1984-91, undated (Box 7)
  - T (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Marcia 1983-88, undated (Box 7)
  - Tendre 1989, undated (Box 7)
  - Theresa, Latetta 1982, undated (Box 7)
  - Thomas, J.T. 1979-80, undated (Box 7)
  - Thompson, Clarice 1989-97 (Box 7)
  - Thompson, Jill 1985, undated (Box 7)
  - Thurston, Chris and Georgia Humphrey 1982 (Box 7)
  - Tillery, Linda 1977-95, undated (Box 7)
  - Tilles, Nurit 1980-95, undated (Box 7)
  - Tofa'ah 1983-84, undated (Box 7)
  - Tomeo, Marilyn 1975-91, undated (Box 7)
  - Tomlin, Lily 1986, undated (Box 7)
  - Topping, Dana 1980, undated (Box 7)
  - Torf, Adrienne 1981-99, undated (Box 7)
  - Townsend, Elaine 1983-89, undated (Box 7)
  - Tracy, Kathleen 1992, undated (Box 7)
  - Tremblay, Lucie Blue 1986-2005, undated (Box 7)
  - Triantafillou, Katherine 1982-83, undated (Box 7)
  - Troia and Grierundated (Box 7)
  - Trull, Teresa 1977-92, undated (Box 7)
  - Tucker, Nancy 1982-2002, undated (Box 7)
  - Two Nice Girls 1988-91, undated (Box 7)
  - Tyler, Edwina Lee 1979-85, undated (Box 7)
  - Tyler, Robin 1979-97, undated (Box 7)
  - Tyson, Willie 1974-81, undated (Box 7)
  - U (Box 7)
  - Urban Bush Women 1997, undated (Box 7)
  - V (Box 7)
  - Vance, Danitra 1984-94, undated (Box 7)
  - Venus Envy 1990-92, undated (Box 7)
  - Vogl, Nancy 1980-87, undated (Box 7)
  - W (Box 7)
  - Wade, Marion 1983, 1989, undated (Box 7)
  - Wallflower Order 1980-85, undated (Box 7)
  - Warnick, Leah 1984, undated (Box 7)
  - Washington Sisters 1985-88, undated (Box 7)
  - Watch Out!undated (Box 7)
  - Waters, Chocolate 1983-84, undated (Box 7)
  - Watkins, Mary 1977-86, undated (Box 7)
  - Weaver, Kay 1984-88, undated (Box 8)
  - Weinbaum, Batya 1988, undated (Box 8)
  - Weis, Sam 1991, undated (Box 8)
  - Wells, Jess 1987, undated (Box 8)
  - Welter, Paula Joy 1995-97, undated (Box 8)
  - Wenz, Annie 1992-93, undated (Box 8)
  - Wernimont, Tita 1984-85, undated (Box 8)
  - Wes (Lori Wesoly) 1988-92, undated (Box 8)
  - Westenhoefer, Suzanne 1991-95, undated (Box 8)
  - Wetzel, Katharine 1980-83, undated (Box 8)
  - Wetzler, Laura 1980-83, undated (Box 8)
  - Wheeler, Erica 1983-99, undated (Box 8)
  - Wheeler and Carol 1988-92, undated (Box 8)
  - Wilansky, Lauraundated (Box 8)
  - Williams, Karen 1991-99, undated (Box 8)
  - Williams, Trish 1977-99, undated (Box 8)
  - Williamson, Cris 1980-2004, undated (Box 8)
  - Willis, Julia 1981-96, undated (Box 8)
  - Wimindance 1989, undated (Box 8)
  - Wind and Woodundated (Box 8)
  - Winslow, Jane 1987-91, undated (Box 8)
  - Winstead, Lizz 1989-93, undated (Box 8)
  - Winter, Cathy 1980-92, undated (Box 9)
  - Wolf, Julieundated (Box 9)
  - Women's Philharmonic, The 1993-95, undated (Box 9)
  - Womonsong (Madison, WI Women's Chorus) 1986, undated (Box 9)
  - Wood, Laura 1989-90, undated (Box 9)
  - Wright, Debra 1997, undated (Box 9)
  - The Wyrd Sisters 1992-93, undated (Box 9)
  - Yagottawanna 1992-95, undated (Box 9)
  - Yer Girlfriendundated (Box 9)
  - York, Beth 1983-91, undated (Box 9)
  - Z (Box 9)
  - Zicari, Leah 1987-91, undated (Box 9)
- SERIES III. FESTIVALS, RETREATS, CONFERENCES
  - National Women's Music Festival: programs and general files 1974-2004 (Box 10)
  - North East Women's Music Retreat (NEWMR)
    - Accessibility: guidelines 1980, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Ads: press releases and media reviews 1982-99 (Box 10)
    - Artist care 1987-89 (Box 10)
    - Board of Directors: minutes and correspondence 1986-90, 1991-2001 (Box 10)
    - Budgets 1981-84, 1985-88, 1990-97 (Box 10)
    - Bylaws 1988-99 (Box 10)
    - Community Model: minutes and correspondence 1988-91 (Box 10)
    - Coordinators/Crew Chief information 1988 (Box 10)
    - Crafts information 1987-91 (Box 10)
    - Day Stage: budgets and information 1981-89 (Box 11)
    - Emma G's Canteen: coordinator information 1988 (Box 11)
    - Equipment/Inventory 1983, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Feedback on Festival 1981-99, undated (Box 11)
    - ID badges and vouchers 1988 (Box 11)
    - Interpreter information 1979-84 (Box 11)
    - Legal documents and correspondence 1982-98 (Box 11)
    - NEWMR I 1981 (Box 11)
    - Policiesundated (Box 11)
    - Performers
      - Audition guidelines and rejection letters 1983-97 (Box 11)
      - Information packets and contracts 1988-97 (Box 11)
    - Planning Committee
      - Minutes and memos 1981-2000 (Box 11)
      - Job Descriptionsundated (Box 11)
    - Programs and brochures, 1981-99
      - Publicity/Printing, 1988-93
        - Site
          - General 1984, 1987-88, 1990-92 (Box 11)
          - Site and lawsuit documents 1991 (Box 11)
        - Site Search
          - Clippings re camps (Box 11)
          - Notes (Box 11)
          - Real estate information (Box 11)
          - Site check lists (Box 11)
          - Site sketches/maps (Box 11)
        - Videos 1988 (Box 11)
        - Waterfront: coordinators and Lists 1985-86 (Box 11)
        - Workers
          - Lists 1990 (Box 11)
          - Applications and information (Box 11)
          - Contracts (Box 11)
          - Newsletters 1984-90 (Box 11)
          - Salary information 1984-85 (Box 11)
          - Miscellaneous events (Box 11)
        - Amazon Autumn Conference 1986 (Box 12)
        - Beguines, Celebration of the 1976 (Box 12)
        - Boston Showcase for Women in the Arts 1982 (Box 12)
        - Boston Women's Music Festival 1975, 1977 (Box 12)
        - Boston Women's Music Weekend 1975 (Box 12)
        - Campfest 1984-99 (Box 12)
        - East Coast Lesbians' Festival 1981, 1989-94 (Box 12)
        - Folktree Festival 1986 (Box 12)
        - Gulf Coast Women's Festival 1991-93 (Box 12)
        - Independent Women Record Distributors' Conference 1979 (Box 12)
        - International Women's Music Festival 1986 (Box 12)
        - Long Island Women's Music Festival 1978-79 (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous Events
        - Michigan Womyn's Music Festival 1976-2004 (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous festivals and newsletters 1978-99 (Box 12)
        - National Congress on Women in Music 1981 (Box 12)
        - National Women's Choral Festival and Sistersingers' Network 1985-2001 (Box 12)
        - New England Women's Symphony 1979-93, undated (Box 12)
        - Northampton Lesbian Festival 1992-95 (Box 12)
        - Rhythmfest 1990-96 (Box 12)
        - Sisterfire 1982-88 (Box 12)
        - West Coast Women's Music and Cultural Festival 1981-93 (Box 12)
        - Women's Independent Label Distributors' Conference (W.I.L.D.) 1979-81 (Box 12)
        - Women's jazz festivals 1980-1986, 1995 (Box 12)
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATIONS
  - Miscellaneousundated (Box 13)
  - Amber Moon Productions 1981-84, undated (Box 13)
  - Association of Women's Music and Culture (AWMAC) 1987-98, undated (Box 13)
  - Beachfront Bookingsundated (Box 13)
  - Bella Via Productions 1983 (Box 13)
  - Bloodroot Restaurant/Bookstore 1977 (Box 13)
  - Boston Women's Music Collective 1976-77 (Box 13)
  - Composers Recordings, Inc (CRI) 1980-94 (Box 13)
  - Eastern Region Producers' Network 1980-83, undated (Box 13)
  - Fallen Woman Productions 1980-82, undated (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Association (GALA) Choruses 1988-99 (Box 13)
  - Goldenrod Distribution
    - Agreementsundated (Box 13)
    - Catalogs 1983-2004 (Box 13)
  - Greenwood Press: book catalogues 1979-81 (Box 13)
  - Greyfeatherundated (Box 13)
  - Horizon Distribution 1987 (Box 13)
  - Hot Wire: Journal of Women's Music and Culture 1987-89 (Box 13)
  - Institute for the Musical Arts (IMA) 1991-93, undated (Box 13)
  - International Congress on Women in Music 1982-88, undated (Box 13)
  - Kate and Company 1993, undated (Box 13)
  - Ladyslipper Music
    - General 1978-86, undated (Box 13)
    - Catalogs
      - 1980-91 (Box 13)
      - 1992-98 (Box 14)
      - Fall 1998-2005 (Box 15)
  - Leonarda Records 1979-85, 1992, undated (Box 15)
  - Macaroon Productions 1975-80, undated (Box 15)
  - Manhattan Muse Recordsundated (Box 15)
  - Midwest Women's Music Distributors 1984 (Box 15)
  - Mountain Moving Coffeehouse 1987-2005 (Box 15)
  - National Women's History Project 1990 (Box 15)
  - New Song Library 1983-89, undated (Box 15)
  - Nexus Records 1985 (Box 15)
  - Olivia Records
    - Correspondence 1976-83, undated (Box 15)
    - Correspondence regarding Sandy Stone and separatism 1977-79 (Box 15)
    - Distribution agreements (Box 15)
    - Information for distributors (Box 15)
    - Letter regarding change in structure 1979 (Box 15)
    - Media 1978-88, undated (Box 15)
    - Newsletters, #1-341975-79 (Box 15)
    - Publicity and catalogues 1973-94, undated (Box 15)
  - Oven Productions 1991-93, undated (Box 15)
  - Panopticon Library 1989 (Box 15)
  - People Meet, Inc. 1984 (Box 15)
  - Pleiades Records 1982-84, undated (Box 15)
  - Putumayo World Musicundated (Box 15)
  - Radical Rose Recordings 1983-84, undated (Box 15)
  - Redwood Records: brochures, catalogs, and programs 1978-2001, undated (Box 15)
  - Roadwork/Sisterfire 1980-87, undated (Box 15)
  - Robin Tyler Productions 1990-93 (Box 15)
  - Rosetta Records 1981-94, undated (Box 15)
  - Sampler Records 1988, undated (Box 15)
  - Shanachieundated (Box 15)
  - Sing Out! 1994, undated (Box 15)
  - Sister Singers Network 1988-2001 (Box 15)
  - Sound companies and technicians 1980-87 (Box 15)
  - Spivey Recordsundated (Box 15)
  - Stash Recordsundated (Box 15)
  - Studio Red Top 1984-88, undated (Box 15)
  - Taping equipment and supplies 1978-90, undated (Box 15)
  - Tape Recording Manual (National Braille Association) (Box 15)
  - Troubadora/Troubadisc 1980-81, undated (Box 15)
  - Variations 1983, undated (Box 15)
  - Vivace Records: catalogs 1995, undated (Box 15)
  - Wise Women Enterprisesundated (Box 15)
  - Women on Stage 1981 (Box 15)
  - The Women's Music Calendar 1980-81 (Box 15)
  - Women's Music for Everyone 1981-84, undated (Box 15)
  - Women Musicians' Cooperative of Washingtonundated (Box 15)
  - Women's Revolutions per Minute (WRPM) 1985-90 (Box 15)
  - Womanly Way Productions 1979-83, undated (Box 15)
- SERIES V. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
  - [This series is unprocessed. Contact the Sophia Smith Collection for more information]
  - Subseries I. Festivals, Retreats, and Conferences: audition tapes
  - Subseries II. Festivals, Retreats, and Conferences: live recordings
  - Subseries III. Record Companies: demo tapes
  - Subseries IV. 45rpm records
  - Subseries V. LP vinyl albums
  - Subseries VI. Commercial compact discs: popular, folk, rock
  - Subseries VII. Commercial compact discs: classical
  - Subseries VIII. Commercial audiocassettes
  - Subseries IX. Videotapes
  - Subseries X. Reel-to-reel tapes
- SERIES VI. SONGBOOKS AND SCORES
  - [This series is unprocessed. Contact the Sophia Smith Collection for more information]
- SERIES VII. REFERENCE MATERIALS
  - [This series is unprocessed. Contact the Sophia Smith Collection for more information]
- SERIES VIII. ARTIFACTS AND MEMORABILIA
  - [This series is unprocessed. Contact the Sophia Smith Collection for more information]
- SERIES IX. OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - National Women's Music Festival: 20th anniversary displayJun 1994